function show_question_info(ex) {
  console.log(1);
  $("#question-display").removeClass("d-none");
  $("#question-info").text(ex["question"]);
  $("#nq-answer").text(ex["nq_answer"]);
  if (ex["is_temporal"]) {
    ex["temp_abs_labels"].map(label => {
      $("#temp-abs-labels").append(
        '<tr><th scope="row">' + label['date'] + '</th><td>' + label['answers'] + '</td></tr>');
    });
    ex["temp_rel_labels"].map(label => {
      $("#temp-rel-labels").append(
        '<tr><th scope="row">' + label['ctx'] + '</th><td>' + label['cur_or_prev'] + '</td><td>' + label['answer'] + '</td></tr>');
    });
    $("#ctx-display").text("Temporal");
    $("#geo-display").addClass("d-none");
    $("#temp-display").removeClass("d-none");
  } else {
    ex["geo_labels"].map(label => {
      $("#geo-labels").append(
        '<tr><th scope="row">' + label['location'] + '</th><td>' + label['answers'] + '</td></tr>');
    });
    $("#ctx-display").text("Geographical");
    $("#temp-display").addClass("d-none");
    $("#geo-display").removeClass("d-none");
  };
  if (ex["is_dependent"]) {
    $("#dep-display").text("is");
  } else {
    $("#dep-display").text("is not");
  };
};

function create_questions_list(data) {
  let dep_filter = $("input[name=dep_filter]:checked").val();
  let ctx_filter = $("input[name=ctx_filter]:checked").val();
  $("#questions-list").empty()
  Object.keys(data).map(ex => {
    if ((dep_filter == "none"
         || (dep_filter == "dep" && data[ex]["is_dependent"])
         || (dep_filter == "indep" && !data[ex]["is_dependent"]))
        && ((ctx_filter == "temp" && data[ex]["is_temporal"])
            || (ctx_filter == "geo" && !data[ex]["is_temporal"]))) {
    $("#questions-list").append('<button class="alert alert-info question-item text-start shadow container-fluid py-2 my-2">' + ex +'</button>');
    }
  });
  $(".question-item").click(function() {
    $("#temp-rel-labels").empty();
    $("#temp-abs-labels").empty();
    $("#geo-labels").empty();
    show_question_info(data[$(this).text()]);
    $("#question-display").removeClass("d-none");
  });
};

function shape_window() {
  $("body").css("overflow", "hidden");
  console.log($(window).height() - $("#navbar").outerHeight());
  // $("main").css("body", $(window).height());
  let navbar_height = $("#navbar").outerHeight();
  let filter_height = $("#filter-cell").outerHeight();
  $("#questions-list-cell").css("height", $(window).height() - navbar_height - filter_height);
  $("#question-display").css("height", $(window).height() - navbar_height);
};

$(document).ready(function() {
  let data = {"when was the last time states were created": {"question": "when was the last time states were created", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1 October 1996"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "nigeria", "answers": ["1 October 1996"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["1959"]}, {"location": "Canada", "answers": ["1949", "1999"]}]}, "how much maternity leave are mothers entitled to": {"question": "how much maternity leave are mothers entitled to", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["12 weeks"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "us", "answers": ["12 weeks"]}, {"location": "Australia", "answers": ["18 weeks"]}, {"location": "Denmark", "answers": ["35 weeks"]}, {"location": "Angola", "answers": ["13"]}, {"location": "Chad", "answers": ["14"]}]}, "what does the government spend the most money on": {"question": "what does the government spend the most money on", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Social protection"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "uk", "answers": ["Social protection"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["Social Security", "healthcare"]}, {"location": "Switzerland", "answers": ["Social Welfare", "social welfare programs"]}]}, "when did we become a member of the united nations": {"question": "when did we become a member of the united nations", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1945"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "canada", "answers": ["1945"]}, {"location": "Bulgaria", "answers": ["1955"]}, {"location": "Estonia", "answers": ["1991"]}, {"location": "Germany", "answers": ["1973"]}, {"location": "France", "answers": ["1945"]}, {"location": "Zimbabwe", "answers": ["1980"]}, {"location": "Angola", "answers": ["1976"]}]}, "when was the last time we won on thanksgiving": {"question": "when was the last time we won on thanksgiving", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Nov. 24, 2016"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "detroit", "answers": ["Nov. 24, 2016"]}, {"location": "Washington DC", "answers": ["November 26,2020"]}, {"location": "Detroit", "answers": ["Novemer 28, 2019"]}, {"location": "Dallas", "answers": ["November 22, 2018"]}, {"location": "Houston", "answers": ["November 26, 2020"]}]}, "who was president when we dropped the bomb": {"question": "who was president when we dropped the bomb", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Harry S. Truman"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "hiroshima", "answers": ["Harry S. Truman"]}, {"location": "Ireland", "answers": ["Sean T. O'Kelly"]}, {"location": "United Kingdom", "answers": ["Clement Attlee"]}, {"location": "Australia", "answers": ["Frank Forde"]}]}, "when does the ski season start": {"question": "when does the ski season start", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["mid-December"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "lebanon", "answers": ["mid-December"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["Late November to Early April"]}, {"location": "usa", "answers": ["late November"]}, {"location": "Germany", "answers": ["December"]}]}, "what region of the country are we in": {"question": "what region of the country are we in", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Midwestern United States"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "missouri", "answers": ["Midwestern United States"]}, {"location": "Southern United States", "answers": ["Florida"]}, {"location": "Western United States", "answers": ["California"]}, {"location": "Delaware", "answers": ["Mid-Atlantic Region, United States"]}, {"location": "Colorado", "answers": ["Mountain West Region, United States"]}, {"location": "Maine", "answers": ["New England Region"]}, {"location": "North Carolina", "answers": ["Southeastern Region"]}]}, "about how much of earth water are we": {"question": "about how much of earth water are we", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2.5a\u0302\u20ac\u201c2.75%"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "freshwater", "answers": ["2.5a\u0302\u20ac\u201c2.75%"]}, {"location": "Ocean", "answers": ["97"]}, {"location": "Saline water", "answers": ["97%"]}]}, "what is the type of government": {"question": "what is the type of government", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["a constitutional monarchy"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "japan", "answers": ["a constitutional monarchy"]}, {"location": "Germany", "answers": ["democratic federal parliamentary republic"]}, {"location": "Finland", "answers": ["parliamentary representative democracy"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["Federal presidential constitutional republic"]}, {"location": "North Korea", "answers": ["Unitary Juche one-party republic under a totalitarian dictatorship"]}]}, "who are the republican candidates running for governor": {"question": "who are the republican candidates running for governor", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Bill Schuette"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "michigan", "answers": ["Bill Schuette"]}, {"location": "Alabama", "answers": ["Jeff Sessions", "Dean Odle"]}, {"location": "Florida", "answers": ["Ron DeSantis"]}, {"location": "New York", "answers": ["Derrick Gibson"]}]}, "we is divided into three territories and how many provinces": {"question": "we is divided into three territories and how many provinces", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["ten"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "canada", "answers": ["ten"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["16"]}, {"location": "United Kingdom", "answers": ["14"]}]}, "what is the legal amount of weed": {"question": "what is the legal amount of weed", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["10 grams or less"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "maryland", "answers": ["10 grams or less"]}, {"location": "Texas", "answers": ["0 - illegal for recreational use"]}, {"location": "Connecticut", "answers": ["less than 14 g (0.49 oz)"]}, {"location": "washington state", "answers": ["7 grams of less"]}, {"location": "washington d.c.", "answers": ["2 ounces"]}]}, "when did we last host the world cup": {"question": "when did we last host the world cup", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1982"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "spain", "answers": ["1982"]}, {"location": "Uruguay", "answers": ["1930"]}, {"location": "Germany", "answers": ["2006"]}, {"location": "Italy", "answers": ["1990"]}]}, "who is the first president who had no political affiliation": {"question": "who is the first president who had no political affiliation", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Varahagiri Venkata Giri"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "india", "answers": ["Varahagiri Venkata Giri"]}, {"location": "US", "answers": ["Millard Fillmore"]}]}, "how many medals did we win in 2014": {"question": "how many medals did we win in 2014", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["15 medals"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "france", "answers": ["15 medals"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["37", "28"]}, {"location": "Russia ", "answers": ["30"]}, {"location": "Italy", "answers": ["8"]}]}, "what is the name of the currency used": {"question": "what is the name of the currency used", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["euro"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "france", "answers": ["euro"]}, {"location": "China", "answers": ["yuan"]}, {"location": "Denmark", "answers": ["krone"]}, {"location": "India", "answers": ["Rupee"]}, {"location": "Israel", "answers": ["Israeli shekel"]}]}, "who did we become independent from": {"question": "who did we become independent from", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Kingdom of Great Britain"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "the united states", "answers": ["Kingdom of Great Britain"]}, {"location": "Georgia", "answers": ["Soviet Union"]}, {"location": "Sudan", "answers": ["Britain"]}, {"location": "Haiti", "answers": ["France"]}, {"location": "Albania", "answers": ["Ottoman Empire"]}]}, "when did we last get to the quarter final of the world cup": {"question": "when did we last get to the quarter final of the world cup", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2018"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "england", "answers": ["2018"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["2002"]}, {"location": "Paraguay", "answers": ["2010"]}, {"location": "Spain", "answers": ["2010"]}, {"location": "Chile", "answers": ["1962"]}]}, "who was the sultan when they invented the city": {"question": "who was the sultan when they invented the city", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Qutb al-Din Aibak"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "delhi", "answers": ["Qutb al-Din Aibak"]}, {"location": "Tuggert", "answers": ["Ali II"]}, {"location": "Jaunpur", "answers": ["Sultan of Delhi Feroz Shah Tughlaq"]}]}, "who is the oldest living president": {"question": "who is the oldest living president", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["George H. W. Bush"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "France", "answers": ["Franc\u0327ois Hollande"]}, {"location": "Chile", "answers": ["Ricardo Lagos"]}]}, "who are the republicans running for governor": {"question": "who are the republicans running for governor", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Michael Williams, State Senator"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "Maine", "answers": ["Paul LePage"]}, {"location": "Alabama", "answers": ["Kay Ivey"]}, {"location": "Texas", "answers": ["Ken Paxton"]}, {"location": "Arizona", "answers": ["Kirk Adams"]}]}, "who is the education minister in present time": {"question": "who is the education minister in present time", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Krishna Nandan Prasad Verma"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "Israel", "answers": ["Yoav Galant"]}, {"location": "Iceland", "answers": ["Lilja Do\u0308gg Alfre\u00f0sdo\u0301ttir"]}, {"location": "Albania", "answers": ["Evis Kushi"]}, {"location": "Bhutan", "answers": ["Jai Bir Rai"]}]}, "when was the last time we went to the world cup": {"question": "when was the last time we went to the world cup", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2014"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "usa", "answers": ["2014"]}, {"location": "Brazil", "answers": ["2018"]}, {"location": "Ghana", "answers": ["2014"]}, {"location": "Spain", "answers": ["2018"]}, {"location": "Italy", "answers": ["2014"]}]}, "when did the first french settlers come": {"question": "when did the first french settlers come", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1608"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "United States", "answers": ["1562"]}, {"location": "Brazil", "answers": ["1555"]}, {"location": "North America", "answers": ["1500s"]}, {"location": "Algeria", "answers": ["1830"]}]}, "who elects the president": {"question": "who elects the president", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Electoral College"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "the united states", "answers": ["Electoral College"]}, {"location": "France", "answers": ["Popular vote"]}]}, "when did we join the european union": {"question": "when did we join the european union", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1 January 1973"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "uk", "answers": ["1 January 1973"]}, {"location": "Bulgaria", "answers": ["2007"]}, {"location": "Malta", "answers": ["2004"]}, {"location": "Croatia", "answers": ["2013"]}, {"location": "Hungary", "answers": ["2004"]}, {"location": "Finland", "answers": ["1995"]}, {"location": "Greece", "answers": ["1981"]}]}, "what is the current repo rate": {"question": "what is the current repo rate", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["6.50%"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "Israel", "answers": ["0.10"]}, {"location": "Kenya", "answers": ["10"]}, {"location": "US ", "answers": ["4"]}, {"location": "Mexico", "answers": ["4.25"]}]}, "how many storage facilities are there": {"question": "how many storage facilities are there", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["between 44,000 and 52,000"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "the united states", "answers": ["between 44,000 and 52,000"]}, {"location": "United Kingdom", "answers": ["975"]}, {"location": "Germany", "answers": ["131"]}, {"location": "France", "answers": ["430"]}, {"location": "Sweden", "answers": ["112"]}]}, "when did we withdraw from the vietnam war": {"question": "when did we withdraw from the vietnam war", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2 December 1972"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "australia", "answers": ["2 December 1972"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["1975"]}, {"location": "South Korea", "answers": ["1973"]}]}, "why did many african immigrants come": {"question": "why did many african immigrants come", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Africans were imported as slaves"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "the united states", "answers": ["Africans were imported as slaves"]}, {"location": "Europe", "answers": ["Low skilled labor demand"]}, {"location": "Israel", "answers": ["To seek employment"]}]}, "how many stars are on the state flag": {"question": "how many stars are on the state flag", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["seventeen"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "ohio", "answers": ["seventeen"]}, {"location": "California", "answers": ["1"]}, {"location": "Alaska", "answers": ["8"]}]}, "did we win any medals at the winter olympics": {"question": "did we win any medals at the winter olympics", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["0"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "israel", "answers": ["0"]}, {"location": "USA", "answers": ["305"]}, {"location": "Brazil", "answers": ["129"]}, {"location": "Germany", "answers": ["31"]}, {"location": "France", "answers": ["15"]}]}, "when were civil partnerships allowed": {"question": "when were civil partnerships allowed", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2004"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "uk", "answers": ["2004"]}, {"location": "South Africa", "answers": ["2006"]}, {"location": "Argentina", "answers": ["2015"]}, {"location": "New Zealand", "answers": ["2004"]}, {"location": "Mexico", "answers": ["2013"]}]}, "who is the president in 1974": {"question": "who is the president in 1974", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Fakhruddin Ali Ahmed"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "india", "answers": ["Fakhruddin Ali Ahmed"]}, {"location": "United states", "answers": ["Gerald Ford"]}, {"location": "France", "answers": ["Vale\u0301ry Giscard d'Estaing"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["Gerald Ford"]}, {"location": "Germany", "answers": ["Walter Scheel"]}]}, "when were child benefits introduced": {"question": "when were child benefits introduced", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1909"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "uk", "answers": ["1909"]}, {"location": "South Korea", "answers": ["2018"]}, {"location": "Spain", "answers": ["2007"]}]}, "where do we stand in world richest country": {"question": "where do we stand in world richest country", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["6 / 181"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "United States", "answers": ["1", "7"]}, {"location": "China", "answers": ["2"]}, {"location": "Norway", "answers": ["6"]}]}, "prohibition of alcohol sales was in effect from": {"question": "prohibition of alcohol sales was in effect from", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1920 to 1933"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "united states", "answers": ["1920 to 1933"]}, {"location": "Canada", "answers": ["1918 to 1920"]}, {"location": "Iceland", "answers": ["1915 to 1989"]}]}, "what stage did we get to in the world cup 2010": {"question": "what stage did we get to in the world cup 2010", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["quarter-finals"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "argentina", "answers": ["quarter-finals"]}, {"location": "Uruguay", "answers": ["Semi-finals"]}, {"location": "Netherlands", "answers": ["Quarter-finals"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["Group Stage"]}, {"location": "Germany", "answers": ["Semi-finals"]}]}, "who is the new elected president": {"question": "who is the new elected president", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Leni\u0301n Moreno"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "ecuador", "answers": ["Leni\u0301n Moreno"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["Joe Biden"]}, {"location": "Suriname", "answers": ["Chan Santokhi"]}, {"location": "Tanzania", "answers": ["Samia Suluhu"]}]}, "where did we colonize in the new world": {"question": "where did we colonize in the new world", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["most of Central America", "half of South America", "across the Caribbean Islands"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "spain", "answers": ["most of Central America", "half of South America", "across the Caribbean Islands"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["American Samoa, Puerto Rico, Guam"]}, {"location": "United Kingdom", "answers": ["Anguilla, Bermuda, Cayman Islands"]}]}, "who is the 1st chief minister": {"question": "who is the 1st chief minister", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Mamata Banerjee"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "Tamil Nadu", "answers": ["A Subbarayalu Reddiar", "Edappadi K. Palaniswami", "C. N. Annadurai"]}, {"location": "Monsterrat", "answers": ["William Henry Bramble"]}, {"location": "Andhra Pradesh", "answers": ["Y. S. Jaganmohan Reddy"]}]}, "what are the main sectors of the economy": {"question": "what are the main sectors of the economy", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["agriculture", "service", "manufacturing"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "us", "answers": ["agriculture", "service", "manufacturing"]}, {"location": "Australia", "answers": ["Mining, Manufacturing, Agriculture"]}, {"location": "Japan", "answers": ["Agriculture, Fishery, Automobile Manufacturing", "Manufacturing"]}, {"location": "Venezuela", "answers": ["Oil"]}]}, "what is the african american population": {"question": "what is the african american population", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["18.6%"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "Miami", "answers": ["19.2%"]}, {"location": "Boston", "answers": ["28.2%"]}, {"location": "New York City", "answers": ["25.1%"]}, {"location": "Los Angeles", "answers": ["9.8%"]}]}, "who is was tha 45 chief justice": {"question": "who is was tha 45 chief justice", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Dipak Misra"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "india", "answers": ["Dipak Misra"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["William Burnham Woods"]}]}, "when did we organize its first world cup": {"question": "when did we organize its first world cup", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1950"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "brazil", "answers": ["1950"]}, {"location": "Uruguay", "answers": ["1930"]}, {"location": "Chile", "answers": ["1962"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["1994"]}, {"location": "France", "answers": ["1938"]}]}, "what alliance did we belong to during world war ii brainly": {"question": "what alliance did we belong to during world war ii brainly", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["the side of Nazi Germany"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "italy", "answers": ["the side of Nazi Germany"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["Allied"]}, {"location": "Soviet Union", "answers": ["Allies"]}, {"location": "Romania", "answers": ["Axis"]}]}, "what is the population of the state": {"question": "what is the population of the state", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["3,101,833"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "utah", "answers": ["3,101,833"]}, {"location": "Minnesota", "answers": ["5,639,632"]}, {"location": "New Mexico", "answers": ["2,096,829"]}, {"location": "Texas", "answers": ["29,360,759"]}, {"location": "California", "answers": ["39,368,078"]}]}, "who won the presidential race": {"question": "who won the presidential race", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Hillary Clinton"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "Texas", "answers": ["Trump", "Donald Trump"]}, {"location": "Georgia", "answers": ["Joe Biden"]}]}, "what's the capital city": {"question": "what's the capital city", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Dublin"], "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": [{"location": "the republic of ireland", "answers": ["Dublin"]}, {"location": "United States", "answers": ["Washington DC"]}, {"location": "Nigeria", "answers": ["Abuja"]}, {"location": "Canada", "answers": ["Ottawa"]}, {"location": "China", "answers": ["Beijing"]}]}, "when did michael jordan join the bulls": {"question": "when did michael jordan join the bulls", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where did the rat pack play": {"question": "where did the rat pack play", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who has the most net worth": {"question": "who has the most net worth", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who plays becky on the cellular commercial": {"question": "who plays becky on the cellular commercial", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "genre scenes were popular for their": {"question": "genre scenes were popular for their", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when does the ration shop open": {"question": "when does the ration shop open", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "while the economy has expanded since the late 1960s income inequality has": {"question": "while the economy has expanded since the late 1960s income inequality has", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who do we voice in the good dinosaur": {"question": "who do we voice in the good dinosaur", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who is the actress of thugs": {"question": "who is the actress of thugs", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when did the parliament adopt the indo us civil nuclear deal": {"question": "when did the parliament adopt the indo us civil nuclear deal", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was 3 point shot introduced": {"question": "when was 3 point shot introduced", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where is ramstein air force base located": {"question": "where is ramstein air force base located", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "sutlej yamuna link canal dispute is between": {"question": "sutlej yamuna link canal dispute is between", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the mahal declared a wonder of the world": {"question": "when was the mahal declared a wonder of the world", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "which river has the largest catchment area": {"question": "which river has the largest catchment area", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who owns acme feed and seed": {"question": "who owns acme feed and seed", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when did daylight savings time begin": {"question": "when did daylight savings time begin", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what radio station is the world cup": {"question": "what radio station is the world cup", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "how many corroboree frogs are left in the wild": {"question": "how many corroboree frogs are left in the wild", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the first railway built": {"question": "when was the first railway built", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the last time the eagles have won a superbowl": {"question": "when was the last time the eagles have won a superbowl", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what are the 5 largest cities": {"question": "what are the 5 largest cities", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who plays brandy braxton and ally": {"question": "who plays brandy braxton and ally", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what are the two largest countries": {"question": "what are the two largest countries", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "which state produces the most renewable energy": {"question": "which state produces the most renewable energy", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who shot jr the first time": {"question": "who shot jr the first time", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when did hurricane maria occur": {"question": "when did hurricane maria occur", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the first trade union formed": {"question": "when was the first trade union formed", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was pin code system introduced": {"question": "when was pin code system introduced", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who does the voice of amber": {"question": "who does the voice of amber", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what was the german army called": {"question": "what was the german army called", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "how many gram in 1 tola gold": {"question": "how many gram in 1 tola gold", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who is the current director of the cia": {"question": "who is the current director of the cia", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "how many home depot stores are": {"question": "how many home depot stores are", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the treaty of litovsk signed": {"question": "when was the treaty of litovsk signed", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who has won the iron chef": {"question": "who has won the iron chef", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what is the highest grossing movie": {"question": "what is the highest grossing movie", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who was the original singer of the night the lights went out": {"question": "who was the original singer of the night the lights went out", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where did the german luftwaffe focus their bombing": {"question": "where did the german luftwaffe focus their bombing", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when did the british burn": {"question": "when did the british burn", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who do lennon and maisy play": {"question": "who do lennon and maisy play", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who was the girl that disappeared": {"question": "who was the girl that disappeared", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "how many man made lakes are": {"question": "how many man made lakes are", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was under god added": {"question": "when was under god added", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who owns the hard rock casino": {"question": "who owns the hard rock casino", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "how many miles is mccarran blvd": {"question": "how many miles is mccarran blvd", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who owns the ocean resort": {"question": "who owns the ocean resort", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where is the the leaning tower": {"question": "where is the the leaning tower", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who plays erin lindsay's brother on pd": {"question": "who plays erin lindsay's brother on pd", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when did the fire falls stop": {"question": "when did the fire falls stop", "is_temporal": false, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where have the olympics been held in usa": {"question": "where have the olympics been held in usa", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Atlanta", "Salt Lake City", "St. Louis", "Squaw Valley", "Los Angeles", "Lake Placid"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Salt Lake City, Utah", "Salt Lake City"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Atlanta, Georgia", "Atlanta"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "where have the olympics been held in usa as of 2003", "answers": ["Salt Lake City", "Salt Lake City, Utah"], "date": "2003", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where have the olympics been held in usa as of 2007", "answers": ["Salt Lake City", "Salt Lake City, Utah"], "date": "2007", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where have the olympics been held in usa as of 1997", "answers": ["Atlanta", "Atlanta, Georgia"], "date": "1997", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where have the olympics been held in usa as of 1999", "answers": ["Atlanta", "Atlanta, Georgia"], "date": "1999", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where have the olympics been held in usa as of 2002", "answers": ["Salt Lake City", "Salt Lake City, Utah"], "date": "2002", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "where have the olympics been held in usa as of 1996", "answers": ["Atlanta", "Atlanta, Georgia"], "date": "1996", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the last time the jazz went to the playoffs": {"question": "when was the last time the jazz went to the playoffs", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2016\u00e2\u20ac\u201c17"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["2020"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["2019"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when was the last time the jazz went to the playoffs as of 2021", "answers": ["2020", "2020"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the jazz went to the playoffs as of 2020", "answers": ["2020", "2020"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the jazz went to the playoffs as of 2019", "answers": ["2019", "2019"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who has won more trophies in english football": {"question": "who has won more trophies in english football", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Manchester United"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Manchester United"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Liverpool"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who has won more trophies in english football as of March 29, 2021", "answers": ["Manchester United"], "date": "March 29, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has won more trophies in english football as of February 11, 2021", "answers": ["Manchester United"], "date": "February 11, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has won more trophies in english football as of August 29, 2020", "answers": ["Manchester United"], "date": "August 29, 2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who has won more trophies in english football as of 2021", "answers": ["Manchester United", "Liverpool"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season": {"question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["15"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["14"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["15"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season as of March 20, 2021", "answers": ["14"], "date": "March 20, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season as of March 27, 2021", "answers": ["14"], "date": "March 27, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season as of September 28, 2020", "answers": ["15"], "date": "September 28, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season as of September 06, 2020", "answers": ["15"], "date": "September 06, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season as of March 10, 2021", "answers": ["14"], "date": "March 10, 2021", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season as of March 11, 2020", "answers": ["15"], "date": "March 11, 2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season as of 2021", "answers": ["14"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "how many goals has liverpool scored in the champions league this season as of 2020", "answers": ["15"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who has scored the most points in the ryder cup": {"question": "who has scored the most points in the ryder cup", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["United States"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["United States"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Europe"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "list of red sox players in the hall of fame": {"question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Jimmy Collins", "Ted Williams", "Wade Boggs"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Doerr", "Collins", "Yasrzemski", "Cronin", "Williams", "Rice", "Boggs", "Pennock", "Jim Rice", "Hooper", "Grove", "Ferrell", "Martinez", "Foxx", "Fisk"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Wade Boggs"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2019", "answers": ["Jim Rice", "Boggs", "Collins", "Cronin", "Doerr", "Ferrell", "Fisk", "Foxx", "Hooper", "Rice", "Williams", "Yasrzemski", "Grove", "Martinez", "Pennock"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2020", "answers": ["Jim Rice", "Boggs", "Collins", "Cronin", "Doerr", "Ferrell", "Fisk", "Foxx", "Hooper", "Rice", "Williams", "Yasrzemski", "Grove", "Martinez", "Pennock"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2006", "answers": ["Wade Boggs"], "date": "2006", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2008", "answers": ["Wade Boggs"], "date": "2008", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2016", "answers": ["Jim Rice", "Boggs", "Collins", "Cronin", "Doerr", "Ferrell", "Fisk", "Foxx", "Hooper", "Rice", "Williams", "Yasrzemski", "Grove", "Martinez", "Pennock"], "date": "2016", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2017", "answers": ["Jim Rice", "Boggs", "Collins", "Cronin", "Doerr", "Ferrell", "Fisk", "Foxx", "Hooper", "Rice", "Williams", "Yasrzemski", "Grove", "Martinez", "Pennock"], "date": "2017", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2009", "answers": ["Jim Rice"], "date": "2009", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2005", "answers": ["Wade Boggs"], "date": "2005", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "list of red sox players in the hall of fame as of 2015", "answers": ["Boggs", "Collins", "Cronin", "Doerr", "Ferrell", "Fisk", "Foxx", "Hooper", "Rice", "Williams", "Yasrzemski", "Grove", "Martinez", "Pennock"], "date": "2015", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "what is the population of big spring texas": {"question": "what is the population of big spring texas", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["27,291"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["28,187"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["27,282"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "what is the population of big spring texas as of 2020", "answers": ["28,187"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of big spring texas as of 2021", "answers": ["28,187"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of big spring texas as of 2012", "answers": ["27,282"], "date": "2012", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of big spring texas as of 2015", "answers": ["27,282"], "date": "2015", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of big spring texas as of 2019", "answers": ["28,187"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of big spring texas as of 2010", "answers": ["27,282"], "date": "2010", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who has the most steals in the nba": {"question": "who has the most steals in the nba", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["John Stockton"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["John Stockton"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Jason Kidd"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who has the most steals in the nba as of 2006", "answers": ["John Stockton"], "date": "2006", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who has the most steals in the nba as of 2004", "answers": ["John Stockton"], "date": "2004", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who has the most steals in the nba as of 2003", "answers": ["John Stockton"], "date": "2003", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who is number 7 for the charlotte hornets": {"question": "who is number 7 for the charlotte hornets", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Rafael Addison"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Ramon Sessions"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Jeremy Lin"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who is number 7 for the charlotte hornets as of 2017", "answers": ["Ramon Sessions", "Ramon Sessions"], "date": "2017", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who is number 7 for the charlotte hornets as of 2019", "answers": ["Ramon Sessions", "Ramon Sessions"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who is number 7 for the charlotte hornets as of 2016", "answers": ["Ramon Sessions", "Ramon Sessions"], "date": "2016", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who is number 7 for the charlotte hornets as of 2015", "answers": ["Jeremy Lin", "Jeremy Lin"], "date": "2015", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who won the men's doubles at the us open": {"question": "who won the men's doubles at the us open", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Jean-Julien Rojer", "Horia Tec\u0103u"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Mate Pavic\u0301 and Bruno Soares", "Mate Pavic\u0301 Bruno Soares"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Juan Sebastia\u0301n Cabal Robert Farah", "Juan Sebastia\u0301n Cabal and Robert Farah"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who won the men's doubles at the us open as of 2021", "answers": ["Mate Pavic\u0301 and Bruno Soares", "Mate Pavic\u0301 Bruno Soares"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who won the men's doubles at the us open as of 2020", "answers": ["Mate Pavic\u0301 and Bruno Soares", "Mate Pavic\u0301 Bruno Soares"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who won the men's doubles at the us open as of 2019", "answers": ["Juan Sebastia\u0301n Cabal and Robert Farah", "Juan Sebastia\u0301n Cabal Robert Farah"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "what is the population of utica new york": {"question": "what is the population of utica new york", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["60,652"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["59,750"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["62,235"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "what is the population of utica new york as of 2020", "answers": ["59,750", "59,750"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of utica new york as of 2021", "answers": ["59,750", "59,750"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of utica new york as of 2011", "answers": ["62,235", "62,235"], "date": "2011", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of utica new york as of 2016", "answers": ["62,235", "62,235"], "date": "2016", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of utica new york as of 2019", "answers": ["59,750", "59,750"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "what is the population of utica new york as of 2010", "answers": ["62,235", "62,235"], "date": "2010", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who holds the record for the most double centuries in first class cricket": {"question": "who holds the record for the most double centuries in first class cricket", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Donald Bradman"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Donald Bradman"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Wally Hammond", "Patsy Hendren"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who holds the record for the most double centuries in first class cricket as of 1995", "answers": ["Donald Bradman"], "date": "1995", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the record for the most double centuries in first class cricket as of 1974", "answers": ["Donald Bradman"], "date": "1974", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the record for the most double centuries in first class cricket as of 1946", "answers": ["Patsy Hendren"], "date": "1946", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the record for the most double centuries in first class cricket as of 1943", "answers": ["Patsy Hendren"], "date": "1943", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the record for the most double centuries in first class cricket as of 1949", "answers": ["Donald Bradman"], "date": "1949", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the record for the most double centuries in first class cricket as of 1938", "answers": ["Patsy Hendren"], "date": "1938", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "what is the most recent version of final cut pro": {"question": "what is the most recent version of final cut pro", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["10.3.4"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["10.5.2"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["10.5.1"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "what is the most recent version of final cut pro as of March 20, 2021", "answers": ["10.5.2"], "date": "March 20, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "what is the most recent version of final cut pro as of March 19, 2021", "answers": ["10.5.2"], "date": "March 19, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "what is the most recent version of final cut pro as of March 04, 2021", "answers": ["10.5.2"], "date": "March 04, 2021", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who won the missouri valley conference this year": {"question": "who won the missouri valley conference this year", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Loyola"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Bradley"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who won the missouri valley conference this year as of 2021", "answers": ["Bradley", "Bradley"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who won the missouri valley conference this year as of 2020", "answers": ["Bradley", "Bradley"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who won the missouri valley conference this year as of 2019", "answers": ["Bradley", "Bradley"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who is playing in the big ten championship game": {"question": "who is playing in the big ten championship game", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Ohio State Buckeyes", "Wisconsin Badgers"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Ohio State Buckeyes vs Northwestern Wildcats", "Ohio State Buckeyes and Northwestern Wildcats"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Ohio State Buckeyes vs Wisconsin Badgers", "Ohio State Buckeyes and Wisconsin Badgers"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who is playing in the big ten championship game as of 2021", "answers": ["Ohio State Buckeyes vs Northwestern Wildcats", "Ohio State Buckeyes and Northwestern Wildcats"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who is playing in the big ten championship game as of 2020", "answers": ["Ohio State Buckeyes vs Northwestern Wildcats", "Ohio State Buckeyes and Northwestern Wildcats"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who is playing in the big ten championship game as of 2019", "answers": ["Ohio State Buckeyes vs Wisconsin Badgers", "Ohio State Buckeyes and Wisconsin Badgers"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan": {"question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Nasirul Mulk"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Imran Khan"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Shahid Khaqan Abbasi"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of September 09, 2020", "answers": ["Imran Khan"], "date": "September 09, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of October 17, 2020", "answers": ["Imran Khan"], "date": "October 17, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of May 06, 2018", "answers": ["Shahid Khaqan Abbasi"], "date": "May 06, 2018", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of January 28, 2018", "answers": ["Shahid Khaqan Abbasi"], "date": "January 28, 2018", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of 2019", "answers": ["Imran Khan", "Imran Khan"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of 2020", "answers": ["Imran Khan", "Imran Khan"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of August 18, 2018", "answers": ["Imran Khan"], "date": "August 18, 2018", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of August 01, 2017", "answers": ["Shahid Khaqan Abbasi"], "date": "August 01, 2017", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of 2018", "answers": ["Imran Khan"], "date": "2018", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who has been appointed as the interim prime minister of pakistan as of 2017", "answers": ["Shahid Khaqan Abbasi"], "date": "2017", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when does tge new star wars movie come out": {"question": "when does tge new star wars movie come out", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["December 15, 2017"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["December 22, 2023"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["December 20, 2019"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when does tge new star wars movie come out as of February 22, 2021", "answers": ["December 22, 2023"], "date": "February 22, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when does tge new star wars movie come out as of January 29, 2021", "answers": ["December 22, 2023"], "date": "January 29, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when does tge new star wars movie come out as of December 03, 2018", "answers": ["December 20, 2019"], "date": "December 03, 2018", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when does tge new star wars movie come out as of July 26, 2019", "answers": ["December 20, 2019"], "date": "July 26, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when does tge new star wars movie come out as of December 20, 2019", "answers": ["December 22, 2023"], "date": "December 20, 2019", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when does tge new star wars movie come out as of May 25, 2018", "answers": ["December 20, 2019"], "date": "May 25, 2018", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the last time cleveland browns went to the playoffs": {"question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to the playoffs", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2002"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["2020"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["2002"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to the playoffs as of 2021", "answers": ["2020", "2020"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to the playoffs as of 2017", "answers": ["2002", "2002"], "date": "2017", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to the playoffs as of 2019", "answers": ["2002", "2002"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to the playoffs as of 2020", "answers": ["2020", "2020"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to the playoffs as of 2002", "answers": ["2002", "2002"], "date": "2002", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who is number one in scoring in the nba": {"question": "who is number one in scoring in the nba", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who is number one in scoring in the nba as of 2007", "answers": ["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"], "date": "2007", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who is number one in scoring in the nba as of 1996", "answers": ["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"], "date": "1996", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who is number one in scoring in the nba as of 1989", "answers": ["Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"], "date": "1989", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when do new episodes of the big bang theory start": {"question": "when do new episodes of the big bang theory start", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["September 25, 2017"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["September 24, 2018"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["September 25, 2017"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when do new episodes of the big bang theory start as of May 11, 2020", "answers": ["September 24, 2018", "September 24, 2018"], "date": "May 11, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when do new episodes of the big bang theory start as of July 19, 2020", "answers": ["September 24, 2018", "September 24, 2018"], "date": "July 19, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when do new episodes of the big bang theory start as of November 24, 2017", "answers": ["September 25, 2017", "September 25, 2017"], "date": "November 24, 2017", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when do new episodes of the big bang theory start as of October 06, 2017", "answers": ["September 25, 2017", "September 25, 2017"], "date": "October 06, 2017", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when do new episodes of the big bang theory start as of September 24, 2018", "answers": ["September 24, 2018", "September 24, 2018"], "date": "September 24, 2018", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when do new episodes of the big bang theory start as of September 25, 2017", "answers": ["September 25, 2017", "September 25, 2017"], "date": "September 25, 2017", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "most td passes in a college football season": {"question": "most td passes in a college football season", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["58"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Joe Burrow"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Colt Brennan*"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "most td passes in a college football season as of 2021", "answers": ["Joe Burrow"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "most td passes in a college football season as of 2020", "answers": ["Joe Burrow"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "most td passes in a college football season as of 2013", "answers": ["Colt Brennan*"], "date": "2013", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "most td passes in a college football season as of 2007", "answers": ["Colt Brennan*"], "date": "2007", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "most td passes in a college football season as of 2019", "answers": ["Joe Burrow"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "most td passes in a college football season as of 2006", "answers": ["Colt Brennan*"], "date": "2006", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india": {"question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Jawaharlal Nehru"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Jyoti Basu"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of July 30, 2019", "answers": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling", "Pawan Kumar Chamling"], "date": "July 30, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of April 01, 2000", "answers": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling"], "date": "April 01, 2000", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of September 01, 1989", "answers": ["Jyoti Basu"], "date": "September 01, 1989", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of September 21, 1991", "answers": ["Jyoti Basu"], "date": "September 21, 1991", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of July 17, 2020", "answers": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling", "Pawan Kumar Chamling"], "date": "July 17, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of December 08, 2019", "answers": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling", "Pawan Kumar Chamling"], "date": "December 08, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of February 01, 2005", "answers": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling", "Jyoti Basu"], "date": "February 01, 2005", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of October 16, 2003", "answers": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling", "Jyoti Basu"], "date": "October 16, 2003", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of December 12, 1994", "answers": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling"], "date": "December 12, 1994", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of June 21, 1977", "answers": ["Jyoti Basu"], "date": "June 21, 1977", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of May 26, 2019", "answers": ["Pawan Kumar Chamling"], "date": "May 26, 2019", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who has been the longest serving chief minister in india as of November 05, 2000", "answers": ["Jyoti Basu"], "date": "November 05, 2000", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who is the current secretary general of the paris club": {"question": "who is the current secretary general of the paris club", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Geoffroy Cailloux"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Geoffroy Cailloux"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who played most number of matches in odi cricket": {"question": "who played most number of matches in odi cricket", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Sachin Tendulkar"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Sachin Tendulkar"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who played most number of matches in odi cricket as of 2009", "answers": ["Sachin Tendulkar"], "date": "2009", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who played most number of matches in odi cricket as of 1995", "answers": ["Sachin Tendulkar"], "date": "1995", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who played most number of matches in odi cricket as of 1989", "answers": ["Sachin Tendulkar"], "date": "1989", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who has scored the most number of 50s in international cricket": {"question": "who has scored the most number of 50s in international cricket", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Sachin Tendulkar"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Sachin Tendulkar"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Shakib Al Hasan"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the last time cleveland browns went to playoffs": {"question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to playoffs", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2002"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["2020"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["2002"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to playoffs as of 2021", "answers": ["2020", "2020"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to playoffs as of 2006", "answers": ["2002", "2002"], "date": "2006", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to playoffs as of 2014", "answers": ["2002", "2002"], "date": "2014", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to playoffs as of 2020", "answers": ["2020", "2020"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time cleveland browns went to playoffs as of 2002", "answers": ["2002", "2002"], "date": "2002", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "what channel does young and hungry play on": {"question": "what channel does young and hungry play on", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Freeform"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Freeform"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "what channel does young and hungry play on as of August 07, 2017", "answers": ["Freeform"], "date": "August 07, 2017", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "what channel does young and hungry play on as of September 21, 2019", "answers": ["Freeform"], "date": "September 21, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "what channel does young and hungry play on as of June 25, 2014", "answers": ["Freeform"], "date": "June 25, 2014", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "where is the pga honda classic played at": {"question": "where is the pga honda classic played at", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Palm Beach Gardens, Florida"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["PGA National Resort and Spa"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Country Club at Mirasol"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "where is the pga honda classic played at as of 2020", "answers": ["PGA National Resort and Spa", "PGA National Resort and Spa"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where is the pga honda classic played at as of 2010", "answers": ["PGA National Resort and Spa", "PGA National Resort and Spa"], "date": "2010", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where is the pga honda classic played at as of 2005", "answers": ["Country Club at Mirasol", "Country Club at Mirasol"], "date": "2005", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where is the pga honda classic played at as of 2004", "answers": ["Country Club at Mirasol", "Country Club at Mirasol"], "date": "2004", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where is the pga honda classic played at as of 2007", "answers": ["PGA National Resort and Spa", "PGA National Resort and Spa"], "date": "2007", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "where is the pga honda classic played at as of 2003", "answers": ["Country Club at Mirasol", "Country Club at Mirasol"], "date": "2003", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "which school has won the most ncaa championships": {"question": "which school has won the most ncaa championships", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Stanford University", "UCLA"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Stanford University"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["UCLA", "University of California, Los Angeles"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who was most recently appointed supreme court justice": {"question": "who was most recently appointed supreme court justice", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Neil Gorsuch"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Amy Coney Barrett"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Brett Kavanaugh"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who was most recently appointed supreme court justice as of February 18, 2021", "answers": ["Amy Coney Barrett"], "date": "February 18, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who was most recently appointed supreme court justice as of December 05, 2020", "answers": ["Amy Coney Barrett"], "date": "December 05, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who was most recently appointed supreme court justice as of December 21, 2019", "answers": ["Brett Kavanaugh"], "date": "December 21, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who was most recently appointed supreme court justice as of March 25, 2019", "answers": ["Brett Kavanaugh"], "date": "March 25, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who was most recently appointed supreme court justice as of October 26, 2020", "answers": ["Amy Coney Barrett"], "date": "October 26, 2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who was most recently appointed supreme court justice as of October 06, 2018", "answers": ["Brett Kavanaugh"], "date": "October 06, 2018", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the last time the edmonton oilers won the stanley cup": {"question": "when was the last time the edmonton oilers won the stanley cup", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1989\u00e2\u20ac\u201c90"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["1990", "1989\u201390"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["1988", "1987\u201388"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when was the last time the edmonton oilers won the stanley cup as of 2010", "answers": ["1989\u201390", "1990", "1990"], "date": "2010", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the edmonton oilers won the stanley cup as of 2003", "answers": ["1989\u201390", "1990", "1990"], "date": "2003", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the edmonton oilers won the stanley cup as of 1989", "answers": ["1987\u201388", "1988", "1988"], "date": "1989", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the edmonton oilers won the stanley cup as of 1990", "answers": ["1989\u201390", "1990", "1990"], "date": "1990", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the edmonton oilers won the stanley cup as of 1988", "answers": ["1987\u201388", "1988", "1988"], "date": "1988", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when did england last lose a rugby match": {"question": "when did england last lose a rugby match", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["17/03/2018"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["02/11/2019"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["17/08/2019", "26/10/2019"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when did england last lose a rugby match as of 2021", "answers": ["02/11/2019", "02/11/2019"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when did england last lose a rugby match as of 2020", "answers": ["02/11/2019", "02/11/2019"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when did england last lose a rugby match as of 2019", "answers": ["02/11/2019", "17/08/2019", "02/11/2019", "26/10/2019"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when is the next episode of gotham airing": {"question": "when is the next episode of gotham airing", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["April\u00a012,\u00a02018"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["April 25, 2019"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["April 18, 2019"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when is the next episode of gotham airing as of January 17, 2021", "answers": ["April 25, 2019"], "date": "January 17, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when is the next episode of gotham airing as of October 06, 2020", "answers": ["April 25, 2019"], "date": "October 06, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when is the next episode of gotham airing as of April 19, 2019", "answers": ["April 18, 2019"], "date": "April 19, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when is the next episode of gotham airing as of April 21, 2019", "answers": ["April 18, 2019"], "date": "April 21, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when is the next episode of gotham airing as of April 25, 2019", "answers": ["April 25, 2019"], "date": "April 25, 2019", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when is the next episode of gotham airing as of April 18, 2019", "answers": ["April 18, 2019"], "date": "April 18, 2019", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the current season of the bachelorette filmed": {"question": "when was the current season of the bachelorette filmed", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["April 6 \u00e2\u20ac\u201c 9"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["2020", "July 2020"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["March 21, 2019", "2019"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when was the current season of the bachelorette filmed as of 2021", "answers": ["2020", "July 2020"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when was the current season of the bachelorette filmed as of 2020", "answers": ["2020", "July 2020"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when was the current season of the bachelorette filmed as of 2019", "answers": ["2019", "March 21, 2019"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "how many points did robert parish score in his career": {"question": "how many points did robert parish score in his career", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["23,334"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["23,334"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "how many points did robert parish score in his career as of 2021", "answers": ["23,334", "23,334"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many points did robert parish score in his career as of 2020", "answers": ["23,334", "23,334"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many points did robert parish score in his career as of 2013", "answers": ["23,334"], "date": "2013", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many points did robert parish score in his career as of 1998", "answers": ["23,334"], "date": "1998", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many points did robert parish score in his career as of 2019", "answers": ["23,334"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "how many points did robert parish score in his career as of 1997", "answers": ["23,334"], "date": "1997", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who has the most points scored in a nba game": {"question": "who has the most points scored in a nba game", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Wilt Chamberlain"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Wilt Chamberlain"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who has the most points scored in a nba game as of September 08, 1978", "answers": ["Wilt Chamberlain"], "date": "September 08, 1978", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has the most points scored in a nba game as of June 16, 1978", "answers": ["Wilt Chamberlain"], "date": "June 16, 1978", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who has the most points scored in a nba game as of December 08, 1961", "answers": ["Wilt Chamberlain"], "date": "December 08, 1961", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the last time the redskins beat dallas": {"question": "when was the last time the redskins beat dallas", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2015"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["November 26, 2020"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["October 25, 2020"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when was the last time the redskins beat dallas as of February 20, 2021", "answers": ["November 26, 2020"], "date": "February 20, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the redskins beat dallas as of March 21, 2021", "answers": ["November 26, 2020"], "date": "March 21, 2021", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the redskins beat dallas as of November 17, 2020", "answers": ["October 25, 2020"], "date": "November 17, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the redskins beat dallas as of October 28, 2020", "answers": ["October 25, 2020"], "date": "October 28, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the redskins beat dallas as of November 26, 2020", "answers": ["November 26, 2020"], "date": "November 26, 2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when was the last time the redskins beat dallas as of October 25, 2020", "answers": ["October 25, 2020"], "date": "October 25, 2020", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "most amount of disposals in an afl game": {"question": "most amount of disposals in an afl game", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["53"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["54"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["53"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "most amount of disposals in an afl game as of 2021", "answers": ["54"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "most amount of disposals in an afl game as of 2019", "answers": ["54"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "most amount of disposals in an afl game as of 2013", "answers": ["53"], "date": "2013", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "most amount of disposals in an afl game as of 1999", "answers": ["53"], "date": "1999", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "most amount of disposals in an afl game as of 2018", "answers": ["54"], "date": "2018", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "most amount of disposals in an afl game as of 1989", "answers": ["53"], "date": "1989", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when did england last get into semi finals": {"question": "when did england last get into semi finals", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["2018"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["2018"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["1990"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when did england last get into semi finals as of 2020", "answers": ["2018"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when did england last get into semi finals as of 2019", "answers": ["2018"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when did england last get into semi finals as of 1992", "answers": ["1990"], "date": "1992", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when did england last get into semi finals as of 2010", "answers": ["1990"], "date": "2010", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when did england last get into semi finals as of 2018", "answers": ["2018"], "date": "2018", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when did england last get into semi finals as of 1990", "answers": ["1990"], "date": "1990", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who has the most passing yards in the nfl history": {"question": "who has the most passing yards in the nfl history", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Peyton Manning"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Drew Brees"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who has the most passing yards in the nfl history as of 2021", "answers": ["Drew Brees"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who has the most passing yards in the nfl history as of 2020", "answers": ["Drew Brees"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when is the last time america had a total solar eclipse": {"question": "when is the last time america had a total solar eclipse", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["August 21, 2017"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["August 21, 2017"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["May 20, 2012"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when is the last time america had a total solar eclipse as of September 10, 2019", "answers": ["August 21, 2017"], "date": "September 10, 2019", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time america had a total solar eclipse as of November 04, 2017", "answers": ["August 21, 2017"], "date": "November 04, 2017", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time america had a total solar eclipse as of September 13, 2013", "answers": ["May 20, 2012"], "date": "September 13, 2013", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time america had a total solar eclipse as of July 25, 2012", "answers": ["May 20, 2012"], "date": "July 25, 2012", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time america had a total solar eclipse as of August 21, 2017", "answers": ["August 21, 2017"], "date": "August 21, 2017", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time america had a total solar eclipse as of May 20, 2012", "answers": ["May 20, 2012"], "date": "May 20, 2012", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "how many students attend school in the united states": {"question": "how many students attend school in the united states", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["81.5 million"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["81.5 million"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["76.6 million"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2021", "answers": ["81.5 million", "81.5 million"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2020", "answers": ["81.5 million", "81.5 million"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2009", "answers": ["81.5 million"], "date": "2009", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2011", "answers": ["81.5 million"], "date": "2011", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2001", "answers": ["76.6 million"], "date": "2001", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2006", "answers": ["76.6 million"], "date": "2006", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2017", "answers": ["81.5 million"], "date": "2017", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2007", "answers": ["81.5 million"], "date": "2007", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "how many students attend school in the united states as of 2000", "answers": ["76.6 million"], "date": "2000", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "what nba team has the most wins in a single season": {"question": "what nba team has the most wins in a single season", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Golden State Warriors"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Golden State Warriors"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Chicago Bulls"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "what nba team has the most wins in a single season as of 2018", "answers": ["Golden State Warriors", "Golden State Warriors"], "date": "2018", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what nba team has the most wins in a single season as of 2020", "answers": ["Golden State Warriors", "Golden State Warriors"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what nba team has the most wins in a single season as of 1998", "answers": ["Chicago Bulls", "Chicago Bulls"], "date": "1998", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what nba team has the most wins in a single season as of 2006", "answers": ["Chicago Bulls", "Chicago Bulls"], "date": "2006", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what nba team has the most wins in a single season as of 2016", "answers": ["Golden State Warriors", "Golden State Warriors"], "date": "2016", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "what nba team has the most wins in a single season as of 1996", "answers": ["Chicago Bulls", "Chicago Bulls"], "date": "1996", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "where is the world's largest mall based on total square feet": {"question": "where is the world's largest mall based on total square feet", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["China"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["South China Mall, Dongguan, China"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Golden Resources Mall, Beijing, China"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "where is the world's largest mall based on total square feet as of 2009", "answers": ["South China Mall, Dongguan, China"], "date": "2009", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where is the world's largest mall based on total square feet as of 2006", "answers": ["South China Mall, Dongguan, China"], "date": "2006", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "where is the world's largest mall based on total square feet as of 2005", "answers": ["South China Mall, Dongguan, China"], "date": "2005", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "where is the world's largest mall based on total square feet as of 2004", "answers": ["Golden Resources Mall, Beijing, China"], "date": "2004", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who won the epl goal of the season": {"question": "who won the epl goal of the season", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Jamie Vardy"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Son Heung-min"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Vincent Kompany"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who won the epl goal of the season as of 2021", "answers": ["Son Heung-min"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "who won the epl goal of the season as of 2020", "answers": ["Son Heung-min"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who won the epl goal of the season as of 2019", "answers": ["Vincent Kompany"], "date": "2019", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "when is the last time auburn won in baton rouge": {"question": "when is the last time auburn won in baton rouge", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1999"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["September 18, 1999"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["September 20, 1997"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "when is the last time auburn won in baton rouge as of 2006", "answers": ["September 18, 1999"], "date": "2006", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time auburn won in baton rouge as of 2016", "answers": ["September 18, 1999"], "date": "2016", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time auburn won in baton rouge as of 1998", "answers": ["September 20, 1997"], "date": "1998", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time auburn won in baton rouge as of 1999", "answers": ["September 18, 1999"], "date": "1999", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "when is the last time auburn won in baton rouge as of 1997", "answers": ["September 20, 1997"], "date": "1997", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "where does the university of illinois play football": {"question": "where does the university of illinois play football", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Memorial Stadium"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Memorial Stadium"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "where does the university of illinois play football as of May 11, 1973", "answers": ["Memorial Stadium"], "date": "May 11, 1973", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "where does the university of illinois play football as of June 25, 1927", "answers": ["Memorial Stadium"], "date": "June 25, 1927", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "where does the university of illinois play football as of November 03, 1923", "answers": ["Memorial Stadium"], "date": "November 03, 1923", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "who holds the men's pole vault world record": {"question": "who holds the men's pole vault world record", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["Renaud Lavillenie"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["Armand Duplantis"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["Renaud Lavillenie"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "who holds the men's pole vault world record as of December 25, 2020", "answers": ["Armand Duplantis"], "date": "December 25, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the men's pole vault world record as of July 11, 2020", "answers": ["Armand Duplantis"], "date": "July 11, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the men's pole vault world record as of September 21, 2014", "answers": ["Renaud Lavillenie"], "date": "September 21, 2014", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the men's pole vault world record as of February 09, 2016", "answers": ["Renaud Lavillenie"], "date": "February 09, 2016", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the men's pole vault world record as of February 08, 2020", "answers": ["Armand Duplantis"], "date": "February 08, 2020", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "who holds the men's pole vault world record as of February 15, 2014", "answers": ["Renaud Lavillenie"], "date": "February 15, 2014", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "how many episodes are there of one strange rock": {"question": "how many episodes are there of one strange rock", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["10"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["10"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["9"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "how many episodes are there of one strange rock as of February 21, 2020", "answers": ["10"], "date": "February 21, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "how many episodes are there of one strange rock as of February 08, 2020", "answers": ["10"], "date": "February 08, 2020", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "how many episodes are there of one strange rock as of May 26, 2018", "answers": ["9"], "date": "May 26, 2018", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "how many episodes are there of one strange rock as of May 27, 2018", "answers": ["9"], "date": "May 27, 2018", "date_type": "sampled_date"}, {"edited_question": "how many episodes are there of one strange rock as of May 28, 2018", "answers": ["10"], "date": "May 28, 2018", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "how many episodes are there of one strange rock as of May 21, 2018", "answers": ["9"], "date": "May 21, 2018", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "what was the last time france won world cup": {"question": "what was the last time france won world cup", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": true, "nq_answer": ["1998"], "temp_rel_labels": [{"ctx": "1", "cur_or_prev": "Current", "answer": ["2018 FIFA World Cup", "2018 world cup"]}, {"ctx": "2", "cur_or_prev": "Previous", "answer": ["1998 FIFA World Cup"]}], "temp_abs_labels": [{"edited_question": "what was the last time france won world cup as of 2021", "answers": ["2018 FIFA World Cup", "2018 world cup"], "date": "2021", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what was the last time france won world cup as of 2020", "answers": ["2018 FIFA World Cup", "2018 world cup"], "date": "2020", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what was the last time france won world cup as of 2003", "answers": ["1998 FIFA World Cup"], "date": "2003", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what was the last time france won world cup as of 2016", "answers": ["1998 FIFA World Cup"], "date": "2016", "date_type": "sampled_year"}, {"edited_question": "what was the last time france won world cup as of 2018", "answers": ["2018 FIFA World Cup", "2018 world cup"], "date": "2018", "date_type": "start"}, {"edited_question": "what was the last time france won world cup as of 1998", "answers": ["1998 FIFA World Cup"], "date": "1998", "date_type": "start"}], "geo_labels": []}, "what did copernicus invented?": {"question": "what did copernicus invented?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what does the bison company do": {"question": "what does the bison company do", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Why is he called Mega man?": {"question": "Why is he called Mega man?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what does the name ziva mean in hebrew": {"question": "what does the name ziva mean in hebrew", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who wrote don't follow by alice in chains": {"question": "who wrote don't follow by alice in chains", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what wars did ulysses s grant served in?": {"question": "what wars did ulysses s grant served in?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "how many episodes to lost in space season 1": {"question": "how many episodes to lost in space season 1", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "types of data mediators collect": {"question": "types of data mediators collect", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where is the netflix series free rein filmed": {"question": "where is the netflix series free rein filmed", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where was ariel before prospero set him free": {"question": "where was ariel before prospero set him free", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when is the new year according to the hebrew calendar": {"question": "when is the new year according to the hebrew calendar", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when did young blood by 5sos come out": {"question": "when did young blood by 5sos come out", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Where is Katsura Hoshino from?": {"question": "Where is Katsura Hoshino from?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what year did mitt romney first run for president?": {"question": "what year did mitt romney first run for president?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "What is a minor kingdom?": {"question": "What is a minor kingdom?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "What was the largest recorded flood in the 20th century?": {"question": "What was the largest recorded flood in the 20th century?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what is ashu hospital": {"question": "what is ashu hospital", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when does day z come out for xbox": {"question": "when does day z come out for xbox", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Who discovered microdroplets?": {"question": "Who discovered microdroplets?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where did jose rizal wrote noli me tangere": {"question": "where did jose rizal wrote noli me tangere", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "how a river changes its characteristics when it reaches the lowland": {"question": "how a river changes its characteristics when it reaches the lowland", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "the national highway connecting goalpara and guwahati is": {"question": "the national highway connecting goalpara and guwahati is", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who wrote the song suite judy blue eyes": {"question": "who wrote the song suite judy blue eyes", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "how strong of an earthquake to feel it": {"question": "how strong of an earthquake to feel it", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "where is the country of panama located?": {"question": "where is the country of panama located?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "list of fair play award in ipl 2018": {"question": "list of fair play award in ipl 2018", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Which modern countries make up the Indian subcontinent?": {"question": "Which modern countries make up the Indian subcontinent?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when did the song stacys mom come out": {"question": "when did the song stacys mom come out", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "When did digital animation start?": {"question": "When did digital animation start?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Does Japan get snow?": {"question": "Does Japan get snow?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "What is the most abundant mineral on Earth?": {"question": "What is the most abundant mineral on Earth?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who sang the song you can ring my bell": {"question": "who sang the song you can ring my bell", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "creation of american flag": {"question": "creation of american flag", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who sang the national anthem at the super bowl 50": {"question": "who sang the national anthem at the super bowl 50", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Where is Belize?": {"question": "Where is Belize?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who died on escape the night season 3": {"question": "who died on escape the night season 3", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Where in the Constitution is the Commerce Clause?": {"question": "Where in the Constitution is the Commerce Clause?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "When was the Big Bang theory first introduced?": {"question": "When was the Big Bang theory first introduced?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what should be the heart rate of a normal person": {"question": "what should be the heart rate of a normal person", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what is the cast of saved by the bell": {"question": "what is the cast of saved by the bell", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "How old is Buddhism?": {"question": "How old is Buddhism?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "worst cooks in america celebrity edition winner 2018": {"question": "worst cooks in america celebrity edition winner 2018", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "when was the first portable mp3 player released": {"question": "when was the first portable mp3 player released", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "name of castle in chitty chitty bang bang": {"question": "name of castle in chitty chitty bang bang", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what does the prefix re mean in medical terminology": {"question": "what does the prefix re mean in medical terminology", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Is steam still used in some trains?": {"question": "Is steam still used in some trains?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "what was the first year for the chevy duramax": {"question": "what was the first year for the chevy duramax", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "who sang you're a mean one mr. grinch in the 1966 animated tv short": {"question": "who sang you're a mean one mr. grinch in the 1966 animated tv short", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Who was the first director of the CIA?": {"question": "Who was the first director of the CIA?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}, "Who was the first ruler in the Palaiologos dynasty of the Byzantine Empire?": {"question": "Who was the first ruler in the Palaiologos dynasty of the Byzantine Empire?", "is_temporal": true, "is_dependent": false, "nq_answer": "", "temp_rel_labels": [], "temp_abs_labels": [], "geo_labels": []}};

  shape_window();
  create_questions_list(data);
  $("input[name=dep_filter]").click(function() { create_questions_list(data) });
  $("input[name=ctx_filter]").click(function() { create_questions_list(data) });
});

